linkbax.com 2014-07-27

# ShareCash - Make Money Uploading Files!

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of ShareCash's policies and practices regarding the collection, safeguarding, use and disclosure of any Personal Information you submit to us through our website. ShareCash respects the privacy of the Users to its website. ShareCash recognizes that privacy of the Users personal information is important and never sells it to third parties. ShareCash has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. By visiting this website, you agree to be bound to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, please do not use any services or products offered by ShareCash. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time and continued use of this website is considered your acceptance of the current privacy policy. If you do not agree to any changes in the privacy policy, please discontinue use of our site immediately. 

#### 1\. Information That We Collect and What We Do With the Collected Information, Including Disclosures to Third Parties.

There are situations when using our Web site when we may need personal information from you. By "personal information" we mean information that is uniquely identified to you, such as your name, email address, IP address, password and user name.

Our web server is not able to read our User's domain or email information. In order to keep track of visitors and to identify our Users, ShareCash registers IP addresses. We also can use the IP address to verify the identity of perpetrators of illegal activity.

Our service collects email addresses belonging to senders and receivers with the sole purpose of registering users and keeping track of the number of people visiting. We do not rent, sell or disclose personal information to people who have no direct connection to ShareCash.

ShareCash might use information collected in connection with your participation in interactive activities, including account registration, for its own internal purposes, such as to respond to inquiries, to enforce the Terms of Use, or to defend itself in the event of litigation.

#### 2\. Other Disclosures to Third Parties - subpoenas, court and government orders, our attorneys.

Sharecash will not distribute or sell any of your personal information to third parties.

However, by using this site's services, you assume the risk that a court or government agency may order ShareCash to disclose your submission and/or personally identifying information about you, or that a litigant, a court, a grand jury, or government agency may subpoena that information.

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person.We may disclose the identities of our users if we are legally required to do so. If a governmental agency (for example, law enforcement agencies, US Attorneys' offices or similar governmental agencies) sends us a subpoena, we will comply with it.

ShareCash may need to consult its own attorneys. In doing so, ShareCash may disclose personal information to its attorneys.

We cannot advise you regarding the law or an appropriate response to a subpoena. Should you wish to oppose a subpoena or other legal process, you should seek legal advice concerning applicable rights and procedures that might be available.

#### 3\. Security

The ShareCash Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We back up the data on a daily basis, and have password protected access levels which insure legitimate site administration.

The ShareCash Web site contains links to other Web sites. ShareCash is not responsible for the security practices of the Web sites that are linked from our site. We highly recommend that visitors check the privacy statements at these linked sites.

#### 4\. Cookies.

ShareCash uses cookies for various reasons in regards to traffic and members of its programs. A cookie is a small piece of textual data stored on an individual's computer which is sent from a server to an internet browser. ShareCash uses cookies to save User's settings, track User's clicks on an ad, and subsequent successful completion and crediting of leads to the correct destination of anyone having an affiliate account at ShareCash. Cookies may also be used for statistical analysis purposes by ShareCash. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie.

#### 5\. Third party cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

#### 6\. File transfer safety.

We accept all the possible security measures on our servers in order to prevent the loss of data, inaccurate use of information, as well as file damage. Files saved for transferring are available for viewing only to ShareCash representatives or via the link that is given to the User who uploaded the file. Files saved on our server are deleted automatically after a certain period of time.

#### 7\. Advertising through intermediaries.

Ads on our website are presented by advertising intermediaries. These companies are free to use information concerning your visiting our website and other web pages (excluding your personal info, such as name, address, email address and phone number) with the purpose of advertising products and services that would interest you most as a perspective customer.

#### 8\. Credit card security

All purchases on sharecash.org are handled by a third party payment systems: PayPal.com, Alertpay.com. ShareCash does not arrange and/or save numbers or any information from your credit cards.

#### 9\. International Individuals

Anyone using ShareCash and its related services outside of the United States of America acknowledges that personal information will be collected, stored, and used by ShareCash in the United States. As such, you agree to the transfer and storage of information in the United States.

#### 10\. Minors

ShareCash is not interested in accepting information from individuals under the age of 18. We will never knowingly solicit nor accept personally identifiable information from users who are confirmed/known to be under the age of thirteen (13). 

#### 11\. External links

If any part of the ShareCash website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

#### 12\. Modify Your Information

The ShareCash site provides Users with the opportunity to change or modify information previously provided. If you would like to change or modify your information, please visit your 'My Account' page.

#### 13\. Policy changes

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time without prior notice. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these terms and conditions.

#### 14\. Additional Information

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policies, please contact us.
